Over time you will
generate a lot of files.
One of the best ways to make sure
that you know where your files are,
is to organise them into folders.
As you can see on this screen, I have my
documents folder here, and I have three
folders on there: Adobe, videos and ITQ.
I've created the ITQ folder specifically
to contain the actual files that
I will require for the ITQ course.
I've downloaded the IPU assessment,
the PS2 assessment, the SS2 assessment
and the WP2 assessment, which are
the four assessments that you will
complete as you work through the course.
Ideally, I would like to create folders
for each of the individual units.
So as I gather information and
download files relating to each of
the various units of presentation,
spreadsheets, or word processing, I
can then organise those into folders.
So to simply create a folder, you would go
to the cog icon and select new folder, and
I'm going to call that WP2 And then I can
move the WP2 assessment into that folder.
I'm going to create another new folder
and I'm going to call that PS2 and I will
move the PS2 assessment into that folder.
Another new folder, which is SS2.
I'll move the document into
that and finally, a new folder.
And that will be IPU2.
So as you can see, I now have
organised all of the relevant
units into their folders.
So when I download the files needed
for word processing, I can store
them all in the relevant folder,
presentations, spreadsheets, and IPU.